{"question": "Was there a demonstration in the middle east", "answer": false, "passage": "fallujah where there was a shootout between u.s. troops and iraqies who had been demonstrating there"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in texas", "answer": true, "passage": "february when the space shuttle columbia disintegrated over texas, killing all seven crew members"}
{"question": "Was there a death in the united\nstates", "answer": true, "passage": "the united states, 284 people died last year from the west nile virus while 36,000 people die every year"}
{"question": "Was there a trip less than two-days ago", "answer": true, "passage": "president bush returning to the united states from his summit in northern ireland in belfast with british prime minister tony blair, the president back on american soil after a quick two-day trip, less than two-day trip"}
{"question": "Is there an election next year", "answer": true, "passage": "re-electing president bush and dick cheney next year"}
{"question": "Was there an ambush in latifiya", "answer": true, "passage": "deputy governor of diyala along with several council members from ba'quba were ambushed and killed in latifiya"}
{"question": "Was the war in fla", "answer": false, "passage": "war in iraq"}
{"question": "Was the bombing in the supermarket", "answer": false, "passage": "ba'asyir, 64, was arrested on preliminary charges of involvement in a series of church bombings on the eve of the 2000 christmas"}
{"question": "Was there a death last week", "answer": true, "passage": "plo leader yasser arafat died in a paris hospital last week"}
{"question": "Was there a death last week", "answer": true, "passage": "paris hospital last week, after a lot of controversy surrounding his illness and death"}
{"question": "Was there a fighting in new zealand", "answer": false, "passage": "days of fierce fighting that shut down the city of umm qasr"}
{"question": "Was there a conviction in 1989", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia, where the last execution was carried out in may 2001 of two men convicted of a murder in 1989"}
{"question": "Were there talks on wednesday", "answer": true, "passage": "wednesday stressed qatar's role in the middle east peace process during talks with his qatari counterpart sheikh hamad bin jassem bin jabr al-thani in paris"}
{"question": "Was there an overthrow in palestine", "answer": true, "passage": "arafat hadn't been i don't know if he's -- directly -- been linked to hamas' acts,  uh,  but he was put in a -- pretty -- sticky situation having to negotiate -- the militants of -- palestine -- the international leaders -- and if it if hara- arafat hadn't -- somehow appeased -- the hamas groups or the palestinian militants,  then -- he would've been kicked out,  overthrown"}
{"question": "Was there a payment in coral springs", "answer": false, "passage": "colorado judge ordered two teen-age girls to pay about $900 for the distress a neighbor"}
{"question": "Was there a threat in falluja", "answer": false, "passage": "these battered buildings hold a deadly threat to british forces in iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a two day trip", "answer": true, "passage": "president bush returning to the united states from his summit in northern ireland in belfast with british prime minister tony blair, the president back on american soil after a quick two-day trip"}
{"question": "Did the suit happen lin june", "answer": false, "passage": "anne-marie sued crichton for divorce in september"}
{"question": "Did the attack happen seven years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "four u.s. army soldiers were killed when a suicide bomber attacked a military checkpoint today in najaf"}
{"question": "Was there an attack last year", "answer": true, "passage": "last year, giuliani said nathan gave him ``tremendous emotional support'' through his treatment for prostate cancer and as he led the city during the aftermath of the sept. 11 terrorist attack on the world trade center"}
{"question": "Was the conviction in sweden", "answer": false, "passage": "indonesia to spare the lives of convicted drug offenders"}
{"question": "Was there an invasion in fairfax\ncounty", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq destroyed all its weapons of mass destruction. the united states and britain claim he's lying, and have assembled a quarter-million troops around iraq for a possible invasion"}
{"question": "Was there an accusation in this\ncountry", "answer": true, "passage": "he is accused of attempting to ignite a dirty bomb in this country"}
{"question": "were supplies brought to iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "bring supplies to iraqi civilians had been on hold for days"}
{"question": "Were they flown out yesterday", "answer": false, "passage": "here this morning and we took about 12 or 13 prisoners, three or four enemy were injured and they've now been flown out"}
{"question": "Was there a trial lasting 2 1/2-year", "answer": true, "passage": "the judge refusing to recuse himself during basson's 2 1/2-year trial"}
{"question": "Was there a war in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "in baghdad, they were all doing the most natural thing during war"}
{"question": "Did the trip happen tuesday", "answer": false, "passage": "sunday to brief south korean officials on their northern trip"}
{"question": "Did the call happen april 14, 2009", "answer": false, "passage": "the btk killer called up a police dispatcher june 2018"}
{"question": "Did the prosecution happen months ago", "answer": false, "passage": "this month o'brien narrowly escaped prosecution over his handling of sexual abuse allegations against priests"}
{"question": "Was there a trial in fl", "answer": true, "passage": "her back to fl for trial on the fta charge"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in a muslim nation", "answer": true, "passage": "the most powerful nation on earth invades and occupies a muslim nation and kills tens of thousands of people"}
{"question": "Was there a enter each year", "answer": true, "passage": "tens of thousands of destitute africans try to enter spain illegally each year"}
{"question": "Was there a campaign in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "us-led campaign in iraq"}
{"question": "Did he helicopter earlier", "answer": false, "passage": "later, he's supposed to helicopter to jericho"}
{"question": "Was there a fight in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "troops to fight in the war on terror in afghanistan and alongside u.s. and british forces in iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a seven-month journey", "answer": true, "passage": "the mars express on its way on a seven-month journey to the red planet, contains really two spacecraft"}
{"question": "Was there a divorce in los angeles", "answer": true, "passage": "hunter, 34, filed for divorce in los angeles superior court, citing irreconcilable differences with the 58-year-old rock star to whom she has been married for nearly 13 years"}
{"question": "Did the killing happen 3 years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed"}
{"question": "Did the giving happen last week", "answer": false, "passage": "we met, early 2004 and that was when i gave him"}
{"question": "Was something secured in basra", "answer": true, "passage": "american units advancing west of basra have already secured"}
{"question": "Was there a conviction in kut", "answer": false, "passage": "malaysia's second highest court on friday rejected an appeal by jailed former deputy prime minister anwar ibrahim against his conviction and nine-year prison sentence for sodomy"}
{"question": "Was there fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "the us is currently engaged in major fighting in fallujah, iraq"}
{"question": "Did the airstrike happen the early 90's", "answer": false, "passage": "apache helicopter airstrike that occurred within the past hour or so, we're now told by palestinians, three people died, 33 others were wounded, six"}
{"question": "Was there a invasion in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "u.s.-led invasion of iraq that began march 20"}
{"question": "did she serve 6 months", "answer": true, "passage": "az troubles again in 2004, she serves 6 months , then the day before she is to be released"}
{"question": "Was the killing in the u.s", "answer": false, "passage": "almost exactly a year ago in madrid, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in israel", "answer": true, "passage": "today's suicide bombing in israel"}
{"question": "Was there a explosion in byrds creek, richland county", "answer": false, "passage": "explosions rock baghdad after dark"}
{"question": "Did the hellicopter go down in june", "answer": false, "passage": "march 24th, after their apache helicopter went down in iraqi territory"}
{"question": "Was there a firefight in the center of baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "marines involved in a firefight in the center of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a war 1994", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 civil war in rwanda, where government-led militia slaughtered an estimated 800,000 opposition, and opposition sympathizers in about 100 days"}
{"question": "Did a attacked happen on tuesday", "answer": false, "passage": "a group of 25 to 30 armed men wednesday attacked a house belonging to a village quack doctor in tultuli, 60 kilometers (38 miles) south of tripuras state capital agartala"}
{"question": "Was there a shooting in the west bank", "answer": true, "passage": "israeli troops shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and critically injured two children, ages 7 and 9, during conflicts in the west bank that erupted tuesday"}
{"question": "Was there fighting today", "answer": true, "passage": "today's fighting in baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a sale a few months ago", "answer": true, "passage": "sold oconer the rifle a few months ago"}
{"question": "Did the election happen in 2007", "answer": false, "passage": "1996, he was elected to the palestinian legislative council"}
{"question": "Was there a transfer in february 2002", "answer": true, "passage": "toefting transferred to bolton in february 2002"}
{"question": "Was there tax in north carolina", "answer": true, "passage": "taxes given to north carolina by smokers adds up to more than 61 cents"}
{"question": "Was there lupus in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "baghdad has had sporadic episodes of lupus"}
{"question": "Did the proposal happen april 9th", "answer": false, "passage": "giuliani, 58, proposed to nathan, a former nurse, during a november business trip to paris        _  five months after he finalized his divorce from donna hanover after 20 years of marriage"}
{"question": "Was there a killing mid-april", "answer": true, "passage": "palestinian cameramen, shot and killed by an israeli soldier on the west bank in mid-april"}
{"question": "Was the election in mexico", "answer": false, "passage": "electoral arithmetic: the states where lincoln got an abolute majority of the popular vote (i.e., all the free states except oregon, california, and new jersey) were sufficient to bring him a majority in the electoral college"}
{"question": "Is the meeting in 2010", "answer": false, "passage": "i offered to attend the board meeting in october 2003"}
{"question": "Was the election in thailand", "answer": false, "passage": "recent us presidential election"}
{"question": "Was there a forum in houston", "answer": true, "passage": "houston center, accountable for causing registrations into the landmark forum"}
{"question": "Was there a assassination in illinois", "answer": false, "passage": "zarqawi planned the assassination of u.s. diplomat lawrence foley in jordan last october"}
{"question": "Was there a pounding in jordan", "answer": false, "passage": "pounded baghdad at dawn"}
{"question": "Was the police take him to the hospital", "answer": true, "passage": "a short time later, two police officers showed up and told me they had to take him back to the hospital"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in a public\nplace", "answer": true, "passage": "who is under attack in a public place"}
{"question": "Were the attacks in oklahoma\ncity", "answer": false, "passage": "attacks in gaza"}
{"question": "Was laos taken overnight", "answer": true, "passage": "laos will be taken overnight"}
{"question": "Was there a replacement earlier in the season", "answer": true, "passage": "our starter since replacing rix earlier in the season"}
{"question": "Was the trial in indochina", "answer": false, "passage": "trial in malaysia a couple months into it"}
{"question": "Did the bombing happen in 1990", "answer": false, "passage": "he pleaded not guilty to bombing a birmingham women's clinic in 1998"}
{"question": "Was there a attacks the\nfall of 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "anthrax attacks in the fall of 2001"}
{"question": "Was he shot in israel", "answer": false, "passage": "palestinian cameramen, shot and killed by an israeli soldier on the west bank of iran in mid-april"}
{"question": "Was there a shot in the mediterranean", "answer": true, "passage": "the terrorists shot him and pushed him over the side of the ship into the mediterranean"}
{"question": "Was there a war in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "war, cnn's gary tuchman is joining us now live from an air base not far from iraq"}
{"question": "Did a battle happen already", "answer": false, "passage": "battle is about to begin, maybe only days from now"}
{"question": "Was there a defeat in kut", "answer": true, "passage": "u.s.-led forces were able to press farther north after defeating iraqi republican guard units at karbala and kut"}
{"question": "Was there a stay in jail", "answer": true, "passage": "they will stay in jail until the trial starts in roughly 18 months"}
{"question": "Did the meeting happen a week ago", "answer": false, "passage": "president bush will leave france in a few hour's time after a second meeting face-to-face in private with french president jacque chirac today"}
{"question": "Was there a sentence in central punjab province", "answer": true, "passage": "a pakistani court in central punjab province has sentenced a christian man to life imprisonment for a blasphemy"}
{"question": "Was the arrest on saturday", "answer": true, "passage": "some 70 people were arrested saturday as demonstrators clashed with police at the end of a major peace rally here"}
{"question": "Was there a talks last\nmonth", "answer": false, "passage": "north korea called off two working-level talks with south korea last month"}
{"question": "Was there a trial january", "answer": true, "passage": "luster skipped bail during his trial in january for raping and drugging three women"}
{"question": "Was there a bombings in egypt", "answer": false, "passage": "bombings in saudi arabia"}
{"question": "Was there a death in a\nparis hospital", "answer": true, "passage": "plo leader yasser arafat died in a paris hospital last week"}
{"question": "Were people injured in israel", "answer": true, "passage": "dozens were injured today in the first suicide bombing in israel"}
{"question": "Did he take over the ministry on april 21", "answer": false, "passage": "tvrdik, who took over the defense ministry in may 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in france", "answer": true, "passage": "the g-8 summit in france"}
{"question": "Was the war in europe", "answer": false, "passage": "iran, hope -- and buzz writes no one wants to see a war"}
{"question": "Was there a charge on wednesday", "answer": true, "passage": "stewart was charged by federal authorities wednesday"}
{"question": "Was there a protest in the atlanta headquarters", "answer": true, "passage": "others at the atlanta headquarters protested"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in a park", "answer": true, "passage": "banks was convicted of shooting and killing a 16-year-old at a park in 1980"}
{"question": "Was the hunter born in new zealand", "answer": true, "passage": "new zealand-born hunter"}
{"question": "Were they charged in Ghana", "answer": false, "passage": "50 executives now charged in america"}
{"question": "Was there an appeal in indonesia", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia will delay the execution of six convicts including an indian on death row after five of them appealed to the supreme court"}
{"question": "Was the invasion into agartala", "answer": false, "passage": "the most powerful nation on earth invades and occupies a muslim nation"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in saudi arabia", "answer": false, "passage": "iranian senior officials were meeting there at home, possibly including saddam hussein and his sons"}
{"question": "Did a missions happen four years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "the european space agency both launch missions to mars this month sending rovers and ashters"}
{"question": "Will they tie the knot tonight", "answer": true, "passage": "the couple is preparing to tie the knot at gracie mansion in new york tonight"}
{"question": "Did the shooting happen almost three-years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "yesterday, 164 days after the expiration of the federal \"assault weapons\" ban some lunatic opened fire with an ak-47 outside a texas courthouse"}
{"question": "Did they succeed yugoslavia a year ago", "answer": false, "passage": "become a deputy in the parliament of serbia and montenegro, the country that last month succeeded yugoslavia"}
{"question": "Did the death happen in june", "answer": false, "passage": "265 people died in the november 2001"}
{"question": "Was the slaughter mentioned on cnn", "answer": false, "passage": "auswitch on the bbc breakfast programme, they referred to the slaughter of thousands of jews and others"}
{"question": "Did the vacation happen in may", "answer": false, "passage": "the premier of the western canadian province of british columbia pleaded no contest to driving drunk during a hawaiian vacation in january"}
{"question": "Was there a build in sydney", "answer": true, "passage": "sydney and we are going to build a monster"}
{"question": "Was there a demonstration against israeli", "answer": true, "passage": "demonstrations are routinely held against israel all over the world"}
{"question": "Was there a hit in the iraqi capital", "answer": true, "passage": "the nine-story security headquarters in the iraqi capital took a direct hit, strewing bricks, masonry and glass across the street in the al-salhiya neighborhood of central baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a conference today", "answer": true, "passage": "he reiterated today in a press conference in baghdad"}
{"question": "Did the q&a happen last week", "answer": false, "passage": "defense secretary donald rumsfeld took part in a q&a with the troops today"}
{"question": "Was the war in kirkuk", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq war, at least 130 iraqi civilians have been reportedly killed since the war"}
{"question": "Was there a genocide in rwanda", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 genocide in rwanda"}
{"question": "Was the killing in baghdad", "answer": false, "passage": "he was killed in action in iraq"}
{"question": "Does he run a software company", "answer": false, "passage": "i ran a software company for a few years and then started my own tyre company"}
{"question": "Did a clashing happen today", "answer": false, "passage": "a week ago, protesters have been clashing with police and backers of the clerical regime in tehran"}
{"question": "Did a talking to happen roughly 18\nmonths ago", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the united states this weekend just as they did last weekend, anti-war protesters talking to fellow people"}
{"question": "Did the attacks happen july 2002", "answer": false, "passage": "1987, after attacks on kuwaiti oil tankers"}
{"question": "Was there a hit in mosul", "answer": true, "passage": "bombers have also hit targets in the northern cities of mosul, kirkuk and tikrit, saddam's hometown"}
{"question": "Was the executions in indonesia", "answer": false, "passage": "a makeshift morgue points to mass executions by the iraqi regime"}
{"question": "Was the hearing in washington, d.c", "answer": false, "passage": "an oklahoma city judge has ruled prosecutors presented enough evidence at a preliminary hearing to try nichols on murder"}
{"question": "Did the election happen two-day ago", "answer": false, "passage": "elected lt. gov, instead of wilder, all those years ago"}
{"question": "Did the meet already happen", "answer": false, "passage": "they are scheduled to meet next in the russian leader's native city of saint petersburg in late may"}
{"question": "Was there a deaths in 27 countries", "answer": true, "passage": "deaths in 27 countries"}
{"question": "Did the summit happen june 20", "answer": false, "passage": "g-8 meeting, us-canada (relations) and other international issues of concern,\" bush spokesman ari fleischer said days before the june 1-3 summit, to be held in france"}
{"question": "Was the fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": false, "passage": "fighting in this area of malaysia"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in the balkans", "answer": false, "passage": "president bush will leave france in a few hour's time after a second meeting face-to-face in private with french president jacque chirac today"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in america", "answer": false, "passage": "they are scheduled to meet next in the russian leader's native city of saint petersburg in late may"}
{"question": "Did the creditors take happen in 1992", "answer": false, "passage": "the creditors attempt to that take money from him in 2005"}
{"question": "were the sales in the 1950s", "answer": false, "passage": "the united states quickly became the southeast asian country's main weapons supplier, and annual arms sales peaked at us$400 million in the 1980s"}
{"question": "Was there a founding in  1937", "answer": true, "passage": "kiichiro toyoda founded the automaker in 1937"}
{"question": "Was there a torture in north carolina", "answer": false, "passage": "torture that have grippedded the country of france since 1998"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding in a church", "answer": false, "passage": "a lone gunman opened fire with an assault rifle sunday inside a crowded mall in upstate new york, wounding one person"}
{"question": "Was there a fight in australia", "answer": false, "passage": "fight on those avenues in that sprawling city of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a negotiations april 23", "answer": true, "passage": "negotiations between washington and pyongyang on their nuclear dispute have been set for april 23 in bejing"}
{"question": "Was there a shooting shortly after\n3 p.m.", "answer": true, "passage": "the gunman began shooting inside the hudson valley mall shortly after 3 p.m. in kingston, nearly 90 miles north of new york city"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in the outskirts of riyadh", "answer": false, "passage": "netanya, including the deadliest suicide bombing ever in israel almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed in that attack"}
{"question": "Was there a war lasting 100 days", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 civil war in rwanda, where government-led militia slaughtered an estimated 800,000 opposition, and opposition sympathizers in about 100 days"}
{"question": "Was there a hired about nine years ago", "answer": true, "passage": "hired her, let's see, about nine years ago"}
{"question": "is the smash through happening now", "answer": false, "passage": "early saturday, more units were waiting in kuwait to smash through any iraqi"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in the bridge in San jose", "answer": false, "passage": "british forces continue their attack on targets around basra"}
{"question": "Was there a war in turkey", "answer": false, "passage": "war in china, she"}
{"question": "Was he released earlier this year", "answer": true, "passage": "treason filed an appeal wednesday in an effort to overturn the guilty verdict against his client, who was released on parole earlier this year"}
{"question": "Was there a take over may 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "tvrdik, who took over the defense ministry in may 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding in atlanta-area", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones, hitting a 9-year-old palestinian boy in the head and critically wounding him, and hitting two 12-year-old boys in the legs, lightly wounding them"}
{"question": "Was there a attack sept. 11", "answer": true, "passage": "last year, giuliani said nathan gave him ``tremendous emotional support'' through his treatment for prostate cancer and as he led the city during the aftermath of the sept. 11 terrorist attack on the world trade center"}
{"question": "is there a meet next week", "answer": true, "passage": "both sides will meet with president bush when he arrives in the mideast next week"}
{"question": "Were there attacks in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "islamic jihad militants are already inside iraq to carry out attacks against u.s. and british forces"}
{"question": "Did the launch happen 40 days ago", "answer": false, "passage": "the second rover, named opportunity, will be launched later this month, and both are expected to arrive at mars in january"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding on tuesday", "answer": true, "passage": "114 people were wounded in tuesday's southern philippines airport"}
{"question": "Did the marching happen yesterday", "answer": false, "passage": "americans this weekend are marching"}
{"question": "Was there a war before march 17", "answer": true, "passage": "end the war by march 17"}
{"question": "Was the arrest in san fransisco", "answer": false, "passage": "24-year-old enrique alvarez, also known as david cruz, was arrested monday in san jose"}
{"question": "Was there a cross april 9th", "answer": true, "passage": "april 9th, about 130 journalists from around the world including myself and a couple of reporters, we were going to try to cross the border because we were all desperate to get into iraq, two days after the saddam statue fell"}
{"question": "Were they sent over the past weekend", "answer": false, "passage": "we sent in one of our companies of about 100 men in here this morning"}
{"question": "Was there an execution in 1979", "answer": true, "passage": "1979 to 1983, he headed iraq's mukhabarat, or intelligence service, a period when the organization arranged executions of regime opponents in iraq and overseas"}
{"question": "Was there a throwing in a village near the west bank city of nablus", "answer": true, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones"}
{"question": "Was there a emerge in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "a civilian government emerge in iraq, a democratically elected one, that there'd be more cooperation from the international community, on both the peacekeeping side as well as the political restructuring that's necessary in iraq"}
{"question": "Did a leave happen overnight", "answer": false, "passage": "saddam 48 hours to leave iraq"}
{"question": "Did the conversation happen 10:00 a.m.", "answer": false, "passage": "the 19-year-old army private spoke to her parents yesterday night pie phone from a hospital in germany"}
{"question": "Was there a war in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "war in iraq to fears that it will lose oil contracts that were sealed with the now-toppled regime of saddam hussein"}
{"question": "Was there a battle in the town", "answer": true, "passage": "reports gone to the town to cover the battles"}
{"question": "Was there a firing in the market", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the north camps, iraqi tanks and guns are still firing"}
{"question": "Did the taking to happen in the past", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the united states this weekend just as they did last weekend, anti-war protesters taking to"}
{"question": "Did the conference happen on friday", "answer": false, "passage": "conference hoon hosted wednesday with representatives from 16 countries, mostly nato members"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing friday", "answer": true, "passage": "bombing campaign unleashed friday on baghdad"}
{"question": "Was the fight in birmingham", "answer": false, "passage": "troops to fight in the war on terror in afghanistan"}
{"question": "Was th killing in texas", "answer": false, "passage": "the last person killed in the washington, d.c. sniper attacks"}
{"question": "Was there a appeal friday", "answer": true, "passage": "malaysia's second highest court on friday rejected an appeal by jailed former deputy prime minister anwar ibrahim against his conviction and nine-year prison sentence for sodomy"}
{"question": "Is there a war", "answer": true, "passage": "two weeks after the air war began, there is no let-up and no effective response from the iraqis"}
{"question": "Was there a striking in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "the large 2,000 pound jdam bombs that have been striking targets sclected by the coalition in baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a blast in the cafe", "answer": true, "passage": "how many people were in the cafe at the time of the blast"}
{"question": "Was there death near the iraq-kuwait\nborder", "answer": false, "passage": "china, the country where sars originated, has been the hardest hit, with thousands of cases and more than 100 deaths"}
{"question": "Did the meeting happen last month", "answer": false, "passage": "today's meeting in paris, where france, russia and germany"}
{"question": "Do you always go back to prison", "answer": false, "passage": "you can go back to prison for violating the conditions of your parole, for a period of time"}
{"question": "Was the war in concentration camps", "answer": false, "passage": "the 17,000-strong farc, the largest guerrilla force in colombia, has been fighting a war against the government for more than 40 years"}
{"question": "Was there a turbulence in lebanon", "answer": true, "passage": "new turbulence in lebanon"}
{"question": "Was the killing in cuba", "answer": false, "passage": "abc news producer david kaplan was killed by sniper fire in the balkans in 1992"}
{"question": "Was there a killing this morning", "answer": true, "passage": "pennsylvania a student fatally shot a principal before killing himself this morning"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in california", "answer": true, "passage": "the first person to be (()) um -- uh -- killed for a crime in california in like, thirty five years or something"}
{"question": "Did the killing happen on sunday", "answer": false, "passage": "at least 19 people were killed and 114 people were wounded in tuesday's southern philippines airport"}
{"question": "Did the crossing happen today", "answer": false, "passage": "last saturday denied turkish troops had crossed into iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a hit today", "answer": true, "passage": "three planes hit today"}
{"question": "Did he take office on february 27", "answer": true, "passage": "he took office as israel's foreign minister on february 27"}
{"question": "Did the call happen five days ago", "answer": false, "passage": "i plan to call her this morning"}
{"question": "Was there a conflict in the peninsula", "answer": true, "passage": "conflict on the peninsula"}
{"question": "Was there a marriage for a year", "answer": true, "passage": "they were married that long, maybe a year"}
{"question": "Was there a fighting in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "baghdad because such fighting"}
{"question": "Did they go back back happen 1942", "answer": false, "passage": "u.n. inspectors went back to iraq for the first time in four years in late november 2018 and discovered no weapons of mass destruction"}
{"question": "Was there a wedding this weekend", "answer": true, "passage": "their brother's wedding this weekend"}
{"question": "Was there a release in january", "answer": true, "passage": "pasko, whose sentence included time served, was released in january"}
{"question": "Did the action happen in march 2016", "answer": false, "passage": "action trends during 2004"}
{"question": "Was there an explosion there", "answer": true, "passage": "explosion there and we understand that several people"}
{"question": "Did the meet happenthis morning", "answer": false, "passage": "leaders of erdogan's justice and development party met tuesday evening"}
{"question": "Was the sentence in france", "answer": false, "passage": "sam waksal, sentenced, 10:00 a.m., local time here in new york"}
{"question": "Was the raid in the sea", "answer": false, "passage": "u.s. forces in baghdad are staging spot raids around that city"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in saint petersburg", "answer": true, "passage": "saint petersburg summit"}
{"question": "Did the fire happen 5 years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones"}
{"question": "Was there a overthrew in israel", "answer": false, "passage": "iran, the reason that you had ayatollah khomeini in power is he overthrew the shah"}
{"question": "Was the bombing in colorado springs", "answer": false, "passage": "terrorist attacks here in netanya, including the deadliest suicide bombing ever in israel almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover"}
{"question": "Was there an elimination in those citys", "answer": true, "passage": "the three assets the intel which they need to close with and eliminate final remnants of the regime in those citys"}
{"question": "Was something taken in the outskirts of\nbaghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "the army and coalition forces do take control of saddam hussein international airport, just on the outskirts of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a birth early saturday", "answer": true, "passage": "a baby boy early saturday, eliminating any chance that the los angeles lakers center might skip a playoff game to witness the birth"}
{"question": "Was the wounding in bagdad airport", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones, hitting a 9-year-old palestinian boy in the head and critically wounding him"}
{"question": "Did the hearings happen in june", "answer": false, "passage": "march 17, 2003 -- with coleman's credibility under serious attack, new hearings for the tulia defendants"}
{"question": "Was there a protest sunday", "answer": true, "passage": "some 2,500 mainly university students formed a human chain in japanese characters spelling out \"no war\" in osaka on sunday to protest"}
{"question": "Was there a uprising for 33-month", "answer": true, "passage": "33-month palestinian uprising as israel removed all major checkpoints in the coastal territory, a palestinian"}
{"question": "Did a pardon happen thursday", "answer": false, "passage": "on friday, after 40 days in prison, jordan's king abdullah ii pardoned the former legislator known for her harsh criticism of the state"}
{"question": "Was there a execution in the country", "answer": false, "passage": "no blasphemy convict has ever been executed in the country"}
{"question": "Was there a life term serving in ohio", "answer": false, "passage": "the oklahoma city bombing conspirator is already serving a life term in federal prison"}
{"question": "Was there a sale december 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "11-billion-dollar sale of usa interactive's film and television operations to the french media company in december 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a phone call yesterday", "answer": true, "passage": "i was on the phone with michelle williams yesterday"}
{"question": "Did the blasts happen a week ago", "answer": false, "passage": "blasts to the south as well so it appears that this bombing in this area continues and we have really seen the most intense bombing of the war in this area in the last 24 hours"}
{"question": "Was there a founding in the early 1970's", "answer": true, "passage": "the national carousel association was founded in the early 1970's by a group of art historians and collectors, including frederick fried, author of the 1964 book \"a pictorial history of the carousel\" that single-handedly gave the classic hand-carved wooden carousel the respect and appreciation it deserved"}
{"question": "Was there a talks in camp david", "answer": true, "passage": "camp david talks"}
{"question": "Was the gathering in karbala", "answer": false, "passage": "several thousand demonstrators also gathered outside the white house in washington"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in oklahoma city", "answer": true, "passage": "the oklahoma city bombing conspirator"}
{"question": "Is there a closing now", "answer": true, "passage": "now is that the emergency rooms are closing, trauma centers are closing"}
{"question": "Was the murder in the greater washington area", "answer": false, "passage": "oklahoma judge has ruled that terry nichols will indeed stand trial in that state court on 160 counts of first-degree murder"}
{"question": "Did the first loan happen in 1971", "answer": false, "passage": "the world bank first offered the loan in 1999"}
{"question": "Was there an attack in netanya", "answer": true, "passage": "attacks here in netanya"}
{"question": "Was there an arrival sunday", "answer": true, "passage": "who also arrived in seoul on sunday for a two-day"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in mosul", "answer": true, "passage": "mosul bombing"}
{"question": "Was there a meeting thursday", "answer": true, "passage": "meeting would take place thursday"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in 1998", "answer": true, "passage": "killings and rapes and torture that have grippedded the country since 1998"}
{"question": "Was the conflict in dallas, usa", "answer": false, "passage": "israeli troops shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and critically injured two children, ages 7 and 9, during conflicts in the west bank that erupted tuesday"}
{"question": "Is the summit in the usa", "answer": false, "passage": "summit with u.s. president george w. bush could take place as early as next week in jordan"}
{"question": "Did they leave in january", "answer": true, "passage": "these soldiers were set to leave in january"}
{"question": "Was there a execution in indonesia", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia will delay the execution of six convicts including an indian on death row"}
{"question": "Was there a murder charge", "answer": true, "passage": "now, willie williams, the little girl's father is charged with attempted murder"}
{"question": "Was he police chief in new york", "answer": true, "passage": "he used to be the chief of police of new york"}
{"question": "Was there a bombardment in the rolling hills of northern iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "the rolling hills of northern iraq, coalition air strikes targeted iraqi positions today in what's been called a ferocious bombardment"}
{"question": "Was the war in karbala", "answer": false, "passage": "postwar iraq"}
{"question": "Did the cross happen between alaska and singapore", "answer": false, "passage": "each day about 90,000 people cross the border between malaysia and singapore"}
{"question": "Was the war in america", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq just before the war began on march 20"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding on tuesday", "answer": true, "passage": "israeli soldiers shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and wounded a 7-year-old boy after opening fire at stone throwers in the tulkarem refugee camp in the west bank on tuesday"}
{"question": "Was there an attack in central baghdad", "answer": false, "passage": "indonesia uses short-range rapier missiles purchased 30 years ago to protect its vital oil and natural gas fields in sumatra, borneo and papua from air attack"}
{"question": "Did they arrive in march", "answer": false, "passage": "both will arrive at mars in january"}
{"question": "Did the arrest happen on wednesday", "answer": false, "passage": "24-year-old enrique alvarez, also known as david cruz, was arrested monday in san jose"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in india", "answer": true, "passage": "india's has been reeling under a heatwave since mid-may which has killed 1,403 people"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in camp david", "answer": true, "passage": "their first war summit on march 27 at camp david,  blair and bush"}
{"question": "are there elections in january", "answer": true, "passage": "elections scheduled for january"}
{"question": "Was the gun fire in a church", "answer": false, "passage": "a lone gunman opened fire with an assault rifle sunday inside a crowded mall in upstate new york, wounding one person"}
{"question": "Did the lander arrive in 1999", "answer": true, "passage": "in 1999 the mars polar lander arrived"}
{"question": "Was the laser used in thailand", "answer": false, "passage": "they had planned to use the laser against tokyo policemen"}
{"question": "Was there a call at 2:15", "answer": true, "passage": "2:15 the next morning, i received a call from the night shift supervisor who told me my friend had been \"verbally abusive and aggressive\" and would i come over and talk to him"}
{"question": "Was there an invasion in the 1980s", "answer": true, "passage": "1980-1988, which when saddam launched a land/ air invasion of iran"}
